A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Secretary's Office, Biographical Files, RG 15 FA1280
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Secretary's Office, Biographical Files, RG 15
1940-1980s
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA1280
109.08 Cubic Feet 83 standard record storage boxes.
Arrangement
As received.
Conditions Governing Access
Series 1 through Series 6 is open for research. Brittle or damaged materials are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Rockefeller Foundation staff files, as well as select files of General Education Board (GEB) and Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (LSRM) staff. Often includes: minutes and appointments, appointment history, personal history, correspondence, compensation, budget appropriations, field reports, travel requests and associated documentation.
- Staff, A-Z, 1940s-1960s; 1; 42.05 Cubic Feet 32 record storage boxes
  - Aannestad, Elling (Box 1)
  - Abrams, Christine Dorsey (Box 1)
  - Asher, Darius (Box 1)
  - Ackerson, Nancy (Box 1)
  - Adams, Gladys A. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Margaret Muetze (Box 1)
  - Addison, Isaiah (Box 1)
  - Agosto, Hector (Box 1)
  - Agzarian, Agnes (Box 1)
  - Ahrensfield, Charles E. (Box 1)
  - Allbright, Sally Joy (Box 1)
  - Allburtus, Anna (Box 1)
  - Alfaro, Jose (Box 1)
  - Alford, Dorothy (Box 1)
  - Allbaugh, Leland (Box 1)
  - Allen, Catherine J. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Charles I. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Dorothy C. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Jessie Lou Tyler (Box 1)
  - Allen, Mary W. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Rosemund (Box 1)
  - Altschul, Aaron M. (Box 1)
  - Amelkin, Eliot A. (Box 1)
  - Amis, Elizabeth Wright (Box 1)
  - Amschler, Katherine (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Asrid L. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Celia (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Charles R. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Charles W. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Clyde (Box 1)
  - Anderson, David H. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Katherine M. (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Chase (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Justin (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Leonard S. (Box 1)
  - Anselewitz, Eleanor (Box 1)
  - Antell, Sara Chapman (Box 1)
  - Appelgate, Clara M. (Box 1)
  - Appelgate, Thomas B. (Box 1)
  - Armour, Alexander W. (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Fred and Grace (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Virginia (Box 1)
  - Arons, Arnold B. (Box 1)
  - Arsonson, Joseph D. (Box 1)
  - Ashford, Bailey K. (Box 1)
  - Askey, Arthur G. (Box 1)
  - Atchley, Dana W. (Box 1)
  - Aten, William B. (Box 1)
  - Atwood, Dorothy A. and David (Box 1)
  - Atwood, Sanford S. (Box 1)
  - Austin, Edith N. (Box 1)
  - Austin, Rachel A. (Box 1)
  - Azevedo, Paes D. (Box 1)
  - B (Box 1)
  - Babcock, Helen (Box 1)
  - Bagley, Priscilla (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Charles A. (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Phillip (Box 1)
  - Baillard, Alice Aleta (Box 1)
  - Baird, Caroline (Box 1)
  - Baker, Alfred E. (Box 1)
  - Baker, Winfield Howland (Box 1)
  - Bakerman, George W. (Box 1)
  - Balfour, Marshall G. (Box 2)
  - Baltazzi, Aileen (Box 2)
  - Bancroft, J. Walter (Box 2)
  - Barber, Marshall A. (Box 2)
  - Barbus, Amelia J. (Box 2)
  - Bard, Florence (Box 2)
  - Barker, Robert H. (Box 2)
  - Barlow, Claude H. (Box 2)
  - Barmore, Nelle (Box 2)
  - Barnard, Chester I. (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Howard (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Milford E. (Box 2)
  - Barney, Marion (Box 2)
  - Barning, Ruth M. (Box 2)
  - Barrus, M. F. (Box 2)
  - Bartemeier, Mary E. (Box 2)
  - Bartow, Anne G. (Box 2)
  - Bass, Charles E. (Box 2)
  - Bate, Eugenia (Box 2)
  - Bates, Marston (Box 2)
  - Bates, Vallrie (Box 2)
  - Bauer, Johannes M. (Box 2)
  - Baynard, Robert S. (Box 2)
  - Bazan, Flavio P. (Box 2)
  - Beal, George J. (Box 2)
  - Beard, Mary (Box 2)
  - Bearman, Jacob E. (Box 2)
  - Becker, Joseph (Box 2)
  - Becker, Wesley C. (Box 2)
  - Bedell, Arthur S. (Box 2)
  - Bedell, Nancy M. (Box 2)
  - Beebe, Emily T. (Box 2)
  - Beeuwkes, Henry (Box 3)
  - Bell, Allison G. (Box 3)
  - Bell, Frank M. (Box 3)
  - Benjamin, Georgette (Box 3)
  - Bennett, Betty Mae (Box 3)
  - Bequaret, Joseph C. (Box 3)
  - Berents, Harry (Box 3)
  - Bergman, Adolph (Box 3)
  - Berls, Warren (Box 3)
  - Bernhard, John T. (Box 3)
  - Berrien, William (Box 3)
  - Berry, Frederick (Box 3)
  - Beveridge, Gerald (Box 3)
  - Bevier, George (Box 3)
  - Bevier, Yvonne (Box 3)
  - Bezanson, Anne (Box 3)
  - Bilash, Walter (Box 3)
  - Bishop, Eugene L. (Box 3)
  - Blackwood, Edna M. (Box 3)
  - Blaisdell, Charles B. (Box 3)
  - Blake, Benson (Box 3)
  - Blanchard, Richard (Box 3)
  - Blankley, Janet W. (Box 3)
  - Bloomer, Elizabeth (Box 3)
  - Bohren, Jack V. (Box 3)
  - Bolsover, Evelyn (Box 3)
  - Bombard, Georgia (Box 3)
  - Bonner, Barbara (Box 3)
  - Bonner, Francis T. (Box 3)
  - Bookspan, Martin (Box 3)
  - Booth, Helen (Box 3)
  - Boothman, Margaret P. (Box 3)
  - Bordon, Frances (Box 3)
  - Borden, Joan (Box 3)
  - Borie, Bettina R. (Box 3)
  - Boshell, Jorge M. (Box 3)
  - Botello, Thomas (Box 3)
  - Boudrean, Frank G. (Box 3)
  - Boulger, Mary R. (Box 3)
  - Bourdillon, Jacques (Box 3)
  - Boush, G. Mallory (Box 3)
  - Bowden, David T. (Box 3)
  - Bowers, Betty (Box 3)
  - Bowlby, Virginia (Box 3)
  - Boyce, Alfred M. (Box 3)
  - Boyd, J. D. (Box 3)
  - Boyd, Mark F. (Box 3)
  - Boynton, Charlotte (Box 4)
  - Brackenridge, Marion (Box 4)
  - Brackett, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Bradford, Holly (Box 4)
  - Bradshaw, Raymond W. (Box 4)
  - Branch, Stanley (Box 4)
  - Brath, Lois Derrich (Box 4)
  - Braxton, Frank (Box 4)
  - Brecher, Jane S. (Box 4)
  - Brennels, Margaret (Box 4)
  - Breneton, Gilbert E. (Box 4)
  - Brewer, Margaret S. (Box 4)
  - Bricker, Ann M. (Box 4)
  - Bridges, Thomas F. (Box 4)
  - Brill, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Brodbeck, Arthur (Box 4)
  - Brokaw, Raymond (Box 4)
  - Bromiall, Dorothy S. (Box 4)
  - Broome, Shirley (Box 4)
  - Broomie, Shirley (Box 4)
  - Brosseau, Josephine C. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Elizabeth B. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Frank E. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Jane D. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Katrina U. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Margaret P. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Marguerite D. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Thomas W. (Box 4)
  - Brutschy, Joan (Box 4)
  - Bryant, D. W. (Box 4)
  - Bryant, Jean Louis (Box 4)
  - Bryce-Delany, W. R. (Box 4)
  - Buck, Carl E. (Box 4)
  - Buckner, Alice E. (Box 4)
  - Buechner, Madlyn K. (Box 4)
  - Buker, Richard S. (Box 4)
  - Bukhart, John P. (Box 4)
  - Bullock, Margaret (Box 4)
  - Bullwinkel, Edith (Box 4)
  - Bullwinkel, Margaret (Box 4)
  - Bundy, Doris (Box 4)
  - Burke, Alexander W. (Box 4)
  - Burky, Earl W. (Box 4)
  - Burnett, Eleanor I. (Box 4)
  - Burnett, Peggy (Box 4)
  - Burns, Arthur F. (Box 4)
  - Burres, Walton T. (Box 4)
  - Burrows, Kathryn M. (Box 4)
  - Burruss, Harry (Box 4)
  - Burton, Glenn W. (Box 4)
  - Busky, Fredrick H. (Box 4)
  - Buse, A. Betrice (Box 4)
  - Butler, Dorothy (Box 4)
  - Bulter, Elvis (Box 4)
  - Buttrick, P. L. (Box 4)
  - Buxbaum, Daniel (Box 4)
  - Byerly, Carol (Box 5)
  - C (Box 5)
  - Cadigan, Patricia B. (Box 5)
  - Cadilek, Arthur (Box 5)
  - Cahill, Dennis (Box 5)
  - Cahn, Mary E. (Box 5)
  - Cain, Thomas (Box 5)
  - Calderone, Hector (Mrs.) (Box 5)
  - Caldnell, Bert (Box 5)
  - Caldwell, E. L. (Mrs.) (Box 5)
  - Caldwell, Fred C. (Box 5)
  - Cameron, William R. (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Donald St. C. (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Frank C. (Box 5)
  - Capers, Basil H. (Box 5)
  - Capps, Edward (Box 5)
  - Caputo, Raymond (Box 5)
  - Carabelli, Angelina J. (Box 5)
  - Carazo, Jesus Santalez (Box 5)
  - Carbol, Kathryn L. (Box 5)
  - Carini, Eileen (Box 5)
  - Carley, Paul S. (Box 5)
  - Carlos, Rita (Box 5)
  - Carlson, Charles C. (Box 5)
  - Carlson, Lonne O. (Box 5)
  - Carney, John Andrew (Box 5)
  - Carpe, Grace (Box 5)
  - Carpenter, Eleanor D. (Box 5)
  - Carpenter, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Carr, George J. (Box 5)
  - Carr, Henry P. (Box 5)
  - Carroll, James (Box 5)
  - Carswell, Joseph P. (Box 5)
  - Carter, Altice Sydney (Box 5)
  - Carter, Henry R., Jr. (Box 5)
  - Carter, Joseph C. (Box 6)
  - Carter, Williams S. (Box 6)
  - Cash, Webster C. (Box 6)
  - Casseres, William G. (Box 6)
  - Castro, Justo (Box 6)
  - Cedeno, Rosemary Linda (Box 6)
  - Cedeno, Ruben (Box 6)
  - Cenkalska, Christina (Box 6)
  - Chadwell, Harris M. (Box 6)
  - Chalvenus, Yolanda (Box 6)
  - Chamberlain, Gretchen (Box 6)
  - Chambers, Diana (Box 6)
  - Chandler, Mary L. (Box 6)
  - Charpentier, Shirley (Box 6)
  - Chase, Janet (Box 6)
  - Child, Margaret (Box 6)
  - Chisholm, Alexander R. (Box 6)
  - Chisholm, Lewis (Box 6)
  - Chope, Harold D. (Box 6)
  - Cibulay, Vilma (Box 6)
  - Cimler, Charles (Box 6)
  - Clair, Audrey (Box 6)
  - Clark, Dean A. (Box 6)
  - Clark, Ann H. (Box 6)
  - Clark, Ellen H. (Box 6)
  - Clark, J. Lyell (Box 6)
  - Clarkson, E. H., Jr. (Box 6)
  - Clawson, Faith B. (Box 6)
  - Clements, Betty (Box 6)
  - Clizbe, L. M. (Mrs.) (Box 6)
  - Clodius, Robert L. (Box 6)
  - Cobler, Louise B. (Box 6)
  - Coburn, Patricia (Box 6)
  - Cockerham, C. Clark (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Fay G. (Box 6)
  - Coggeshall, Lowell T. (Box 6)
  - Coisson, Betty Fanny (Box 6)
  - Coker, Martha (Box 6)
  - Coles, Robert (Box 6)
  - Collier, Anne (Box 6)
  - Collier, Isabel (Box 6)
  - Collins, Ralph K. (Box 6)
  - Collins, Ralph K. (Mrs.) (Box 6)
  - Colvard, D. W. (Box 6)
  - Colwell, Howard S. (Box 6)
  - Colwell, William E. (Box 6)
  - Compton, Eric Nicholas (Box 6)
  - Compton, Jessie (Box 7)
  - Coniglio, Louise (Box 7)
  - Connell, Thomas R. (Box 7)
  - Connell, William J. (Box 7)
  - Conner, Corrine Thomas (Box 7)
  - Connolly, Joel I. (Box 7)
  - Connor, Michael E. (Box 7)
  - Cooper, Marvin (Box 7)
  - Coon, Bertha (Box 7)
  - Corbett, Sybil (Box 7)
  - Cormier, Jean (Box 7)
  - Corre, Suzan (Box 7)
  - Cort, W. W. (Box 7)
  - Corwin, Janet D. (Box 7)
  - Courell, Frances (Box 7)
  - Cotterill, Anna W. (Box 7)
  - Coutant, Albert F. (Box 7)
  - Covington, P. W. (Box 7)
  - Cox, Charles R. (Box 7)
  - Cox, Gertrude M. (Box 7)
  - Cox, Jane (Box 7)
  - Craft, Elisabeth W. (Box 7)
  - Craig, Edward M. (Box 7)
  - Cramblitt, Mary Vie (Box 7)
  - Crandall, Carolyn C. (Box 7)
  - Crane, Nancy S. (Box 7)
  - Crawford, Mary (Box 7)
  - Crawford, Nancy (Box 7)
  - Crawford, Porter J. (Box 7)
  - Creelman, Prescott A. (Box 7)
  - Criddle, Wayne D. (Box 7)
  - Cross, Chaillos (Box 7)
  - Cross, Howard B. (Box 7)
  - Crouch, J. H. (Box 7)
  - Crowell, F. Elisabeth (Box 7)
  - Cruz, Robert M. (Box 8)
  - Cullen, Mary Rose (Box 8)
  - Cumiskey, Nellie (Box 8)
  - Cumming, James G. (Box 8)
  - Cuca, Manuel G. (Box 8)
  - Cunningham, Jean F. (Box 8)
  - Cunningham, John S. (Box 8)
  - Curd, Mary Jean (Box 8)
  - Curry, Lillie Mae (Box 8)
  - Curtis, Carla (Box 8)
  - Curtis, Gernville F. (Box 8)
  - Cushman, Elizabeth B. (Box 8)
  - Cyrus, Campbell (Box 8)
  - D (Box 8)
  - Dahl, Helen C. (Box 8)
  - Daily, Ellen M. (Box 8)
  - Dalton, Jack (Box 8)
  - Daly, Nora (Box 8)
  - Dana, Jean C. (Box 8)
  - Daniels, Julius Dun (Box 8)
  - Darbee, Elizabeth O. (Box 8)
  - Darling, Samuel T. (Box 8)
  - Darling, Samuel T. (Mrs.) (Box 8)
  - Darrow, Joan (Box 8)
  - Dashiell, L. M. (Box 8)
  - Davidson, William (Box 8)
  - Davis, Gordon E. (Box 8)
  - Davis, Nelson C. (Box 8)
  - Davis, Louise Coplan (Box 8)
  - Davis, Robert B., Jr. (Box 8)
  - Davis, William A. (Box 8)
  - Davison, Lilla Thorne (Box 8)
  - Dawson, Challis H. (Box 8)
  - Dawson, Josephine (Box 8)
  - Day, Edmund E. (Box 8)
  - Dean, Rollin C. (Box 8)
  - Deane, Herbert A. (Box 8)
  - Decker, Ella M. (Box 8)
  - Dedrick, Helen (Box 8)
  - Deganhardt, Royala (Box 8)
  - De Graff, Herrell (Box 8)
  - Delafield, Kate (Box 8)
  - Denney, Virginia S. (Box 8)
  - Dershimier, F. W. (Box 8)
  - Deruguine, Tanya (Box 8)
  - Dessau, Jeanette (Box 8)
  - Deuschle, Kurt (Box 8)
  - De Windt, Laurence C. (Box 8)
  - Dibble, Annette H. (Box 8)
  - Dibble, Judith A. (Box 8)
  - Dickelman, Patricia (Box 8)
  - Dieterich, Frederick H. (Box 8)
  - Dietze, Ruth E. (Box 8)
  - Disciullo, Mary H. (Box 8)
  - Dobson, Valerie (Box 8)
  - Docherty, John F. (Box 9)
  - Dodge, Constance (Box 9)
  - Dollard, John (Box 9)
  - Donally, Dorothy (Box 9)
  - Dooley, Thomas F. (Box 9)
  - Doull, James A. (Box 9)
  - Dowdy, Lewis C. (Box 9)
  - Downs, Barbara Y. (Box 9)
  - Doyle, William J. (Box 9)
  - Duarte, B. (Box 9)
  - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 9)
  - Dubois, Arden (Box 9)
  - Dugan, Doris C. (Box 9)
  - Dukes, Charles E. (Box 9)
  - Dumont, William H. (Box 9)
  - Duncan, Leila H. (Box 9)
  - Dundon, Mary M. (Box 9)
  - Dunham, Helen (Box 9)
  - Dunham, Joan S. (Box 9)
  - Dunn, Lawrence H. (Box 9)
  - Dunne, Alice P. (Box 9)
  - Dunseath, Margaret Ann (Box 9)
  - DuPuy, Kathryn (Box 9)
  - Dvorak, Bozena (Box 9)
  - Dyer, Brian (Box 9)
  - E (Box 9)
  - Earle, Walter C. (Box 9)
  - Eastman, Frederick W. (Box 9)
  - Easton, Monroe D. (Box 9)
  - Ebertz, Johanna (Box 9)
  - Ebertz, Margaret Mary (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Anita (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Anne (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Clark (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Edgar O. (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Edith (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Sherrod (Box 9)
  - Efferson, John N. (Box 9)
  - Elderton, Marion (Box 9)
  - Einstein, Iolanda (Box 9)
  - Elliot, Ethel (Box 9)
  - Ellis, Elmer (Box 9)
  - Ellsworth, Ruth B. (Box 9)
  - Ellwood, Paul M. (Box 9)
  - Elmendorf, John E. (Box 10)
  - Elvin, Ruth M. (Box 10)
  - Emerson, Edward (Box 10)
  - Emerson, Joanne (Box 10)
  - Emerson, Margaret (Box 10)
  - Ellington, William E. (Box 10)
  - Epps, Preston (Box 10)
  - Epstein, Marilyn G. (Box 10)
  - Erikson, George E. (Box 10)
  - Esbach, Rebecca M. (Box 10)
  - Eskenazi, Elaine (Box 10)
  - Estanguet, Anne (Box 10)
  - Evans, Damon L. (Box 10)
  - Evans, Eleanor B. (Box 10)
  - Evans, Florence P. (Box 10)
  - Evans, Louis H. (Box 10)
  - Evans, Susan (Box 10)
  - F (Box 10)
  - Facciolo, Elvira (Box 10)
  - Fairchild, A. Graham Bell (Box 10)
  - Faison, Arthur R. (Box 10)
  - Faires, George B. (Box 10)
  - Fales, William I. (Box 10)
  - Farnsworth, Emilie D. (Box 10)
  - Farrand, Livingston (Box 10)
  - Farwell, Elizabeth (Box 10)
  - Feiffer, Alice (Box 10)
  - Fenderson, Walter E. (Box 10)
  - Ferguson, Louise (Box 10)
  - Fernandex, Gloria E. R. (Box 10)
  - Ferrell, John A. (Box 10)
  - Ferrero, Renita (Box 10)
  - Field, Helen (Box 10)
  - Fields, Joan M. (Box 10)
  - Fields, Kenneth (Box 10)
  - Filley, Joan D. (Box 10)
  - Finckel, Steven G. (Box 10)
  - Fiorello, Josephine R. (Box 10)
  - Fitzgerald, Alice (Box 10)
  - Fitzrandolph, Hazel (Box 10)
  - Flack, Frances E. (Box 10)
  - Flahiff, Edward W. (Box 10)
  - Flanigan, George A. (Box 10)
  - Fleishman, Mary J. (Box 10)
  - Fleming, Catherine (Box 10)
  - Fleming, William L. (Box 10)
  - Fletcher, Alfred H. (Box 10)
  - Fletcher, Justine H. (Box 10)
  - Foley, Dorothy (Box 10)
  - Folks, Homer (Box 10)
  - Foote, Margery (Box 10)
  - Ford, Wallace (Box 10)
  - Forsbeck, Filip C. (Box 11)
  - Forsythe, Warren E. (Box 11)
  - Fox, John P. (Box 11)
  - Fowle, Jean S. (Box 11)
  - Francis, Thomas (Box 11)
  - Frank, Phyllis E. (Box 11)
  - Fransioli, Mildred P. (Box 11)
  - Fraser, Donald S. (Box 11)
  - Freeman, Allen W. (Box 11)
  - Freese, Herbert L. (Box 11)
  - French, Nathalie H. (Box 11)
  - Freyer, Marina P. (Box 11)
  - Fried, Alexander (Box 11)
  - Friedewald, William F. (Box 11)
  - Friou, George (Box 11)
  - Frommelt, Charlotte (Box 11)
  - Frobisher, Martin, Jr. (Box 11)
  - Funk, Helen S. (Box 11)
  - G (Box 11)
  - Gage, Elliot, H. (Box 11)
  - Gage, Irving Lee (Box 11)
  - Galvin, Katherine (Box 11)
  - Ganakas, Katherine E. (Box 11)
  - Ganzel, Marion C. B. (Box 11)
  - Garbers, Gertrude E. (Box 11)
  - Gardner, Powell B. (Box 11)
  - Gardner, Virginia K. (Box 11)
  - Garner, Marvin P. (Box 11)
  - Gass, Rayden S. (Box 11)
  - Gauss, Frederick E. (Box 11)
  - Gay, Edwin Frances (Box 11)
  - Gaynor, Mary S. (Box 11)
  - Gearey, Verne Smith (Box 11)
  - Geddes, Robert L. (Box 11)
  - Gee, N. Gist (Box 11)
  - Geiger, Jack (Box 11)
  - Geile, Doris (Box 11)
  - Geisseler, Lillian (Box 11)
  - Gelfand, Henry (Box 11)
  - Georgeades, Olga (Box 12)
  - Giddings, L. Margaret (Box 12)
  - Giffin, Ann M. (Box 12)
  - Gilbert, Francis P. (Box 12)
  - Giles, Lillian (Box 12)
  - Giles, William L. (Box 12)
  - Gill, Daniel G. (Box 12)
  - Gilles, Kenneth A. (Box 12)
  - Gillette, Irene (Box 12)
  - Gillette, Lois (Box 12)
  - Gilmore, Grace (Box 12)
  - Gillmore, Raymond M. (Box 12)
  - Gilpatric, Chadbourne (Box 12)
  - Glasounoff, Viadimir (Box 12)
  - Glavin, Rosemary R. (Box 12)
  - Glover, Katherine D. (Box 12)
  - Glover, Lois (Box 12)
  - Godden, Ronald (Box 12)
  - Godfrey, Jane (Box 12)
  - Goff, Hazel A. (Box 12)
  - Goldman, Alvin (Box 12)
  - Gomez, Gonzalo (Box 12)
  - Goodman, A. M. (Box 12)
  - Goodner, Kenneth (Box 12)
  - Goodwin, Evelyn (Box 12)
  - Gordon, John E. (Box 12)
  - Gorgas, William C. (Box 12)
  - Gorman, Arthur E. (Box 12)
  - Gorman, Joan (Box 12)
  - Gorman, Judith (Box 12)
  - Gottdank, Mildred (Box 12)
  - Graham, Arthur H. (Box 12)
  - Grahn, William (Box 12)
  - Grain, Alice K. (Box 12)
  - Grandin, Ann L. (Box 12)
  - Grant, Harry G. (Box 12)
  - Graupner, Agnes L. (Box 12)
  - Gray, Alice (Box 12)
  - Gray, George N. (Box 12)
  - Gray, Joan (Box 12)
  - Greece, Natalie S. (Box 12)
  - Green, Howard W. (Box 12)
  - Greenbaum, Patricia D. (Box 12)
  - Greenberg, Francine (Box 12)
  - Greene, Roger S. (Box 12)
  - Grieco, Frances M. (Box 12)
  - Griswold, Don M. (Box 12)
  - Groenwold, Cecilia (Box 12)
  - Grossman, Rima (Box 12)
  - Grover, Dorothy (Box 12)
  - Gudmundsen, Berit (Box 12)
  - Guild, Cameron S. (Box 12)
  - Guiteras, Juan (Box 12)
  - Gunn, Selskar M. (Box 12)
  - Gutherie, Joan (Box 12)
  - Gutherie, Mary E. (Box 12)
  - Gutterman, Elayne (Box 12)
  - Gwathmey, Mary (Box 12)
  - H (Box 12)
  - Haagen, N. Eugene (Box 12)
  - Hackett, Lewis W. (Box 13)
  - Haddow, Alexander W. (Box 13)
  - Hahn, Richard G. (Box 13)
  - Hakansson, Eric G. (Box 13)
  - Hall, Margaret S. (Box 13)
  - Hallenbeck, Robert (Box 13)
  - Hamilton, Doris (Box 13)
  - Hamilton, Elizabeth V. (Box 13)
  - Hamilton, John H. (Box 13)
  - Hammer, Don (Box 13)
  - Hampton, George G. (Box 13)
  - Hanby, Bernadine C. (Box 13)
  - Hanford, George H. (Box 13)
  - Hannon, Margaret (Box 13)
  - Hansen, Lillian (Box 13)
  - Hansens, Elton J. (Box 13)
  - Hanson, Frank B. (Box 13)
  - Hanson, Henry (Box 13)
  - Hardy, Albert V. (Box 13)
  - Harney, Frank (Box 13)
  - Harrington, James B. (Box 13)
  - Harris, Charles (Box 13)
  - Harris, Shirley (Box 13)
  - Harris, W. B. (Box 13)
  - Harrison, Aleck P. (Box 13)
  - Harrison, Leonard V. (Box 13)
  - Harsham, Philip (Box 13)
  - Hartle, Virginia H. (Box 13)
  - Hartlib, Robert E. (Box 13)
  - Hastings, Lee G. (Box 13)
  - Hausheer, Walter C. (Box 13)
  - Havighurst, Robert J. (Box 13)
  - Hayes, Eileen S. (Box 13)
  - Hayes, Ruby P. (Box 13)
  - Hayes, Wilhemina C. (Box 13)
  - Hayne, Theodore B. (Box 14)
  - Hayne, Theodore B. (Mrs.) (Box 14)
  - Haynes, Arthur K. (Box 14)
  - Heath, Anita M. (Box 14)
  - Heckman, Edith M. (Box 14)
  - Hedrich, Lucille (Box 14)
  - Heiser, Victor G. (Box 14)
  - Henderson, Jane (Box 14)
  - Henderson, Vivian (Box 14)
  - Henny, George J. (Box 14)
  - Henry, Royal (Box 14)
  - Hepburn, Muriel A. (Box 14)
  - Herben, Jean Gowra (Box 14)
  - Herr, Michael (Box 14)
  - Hersey, Margaret H. (Box 14)
  - Hess, Janet (Box 14)
  - Hewlett, Dorothy A. (Box 14)
  - Hicks, Grace V. (Box 14)
  - Hidey, Sally (Box 14)
  - Hierholtzer. Carolyn (Box 14)
  - Higginbotham, Thomas J. (Box 14)
  - Hill, Iris L. (Box 14)
  - Hill, Rolla B. (Box 14)
  - Hillesum, Theodore (Box 14)
  - Hingst, H. E. (Box 14)
  - Hirschman, Albert O. (Box 14)
  - Hirst, George K. (Box 14)
  - Hoffman, Lois (Box 14)
  - Hoffman, William A. (Box 14)
  - Hogan, Francis P. (Box 14)
  - Hohorst, Joan (Box 14)
  - Holbrook, Jane A. (Box 14)
  - Holdworth, Mary V. (Box 14)
  - Holl, Marian J. (Box 14)
  - Holland, Sidney W. (Box 14)
  - Hollister, Emily H. (Box 14)
  - Honig, Florence (Box 14)
  - Honig, John T. (Box 14)
  - Hooper, Ruth T. (Box 14)
  - Hoops, A. L. (Box 14)
  - Hoover, Anne (Box 14)
  - Hopkins, Pricilla (Box 14)
  - Horatio, Charles (Box 14)
  - Horrsfall, Frank L., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Hoskins, Meredith (Box 15)
  - Houbold, Ellenor (Box 15)
  - Hourigan, Mary C. (Box 15)
  - Houts, Dorothy C. (Box 15)
  - Hovland, Carl I. (Box 15)
  - Howard, Hector H. (Box 15)
  - Howard, Jeanne (Box 15)
  - Howe, George E. (Box 15)
  - Howell, Edgar A. (Box 15)
  - Howell, Flora B. (Box 15)
  - Hudson, N. Paul (Box 15)
  - Huestis, Jane (Box 15)
  - Hughes, James G. (Box 15)
  - Hughes, Thomas P. (Box 15)
  - Hulse, Fernald E. (Box 15)
  - Hunt, Barbara (Box 15)
  - Huntley, Ruth N. (Box 15)
  - Hurt, Suzanne (Box 15)
  - Huvane, Mary K. (Box 15)
  - Hydrick, John L. (Box 15)
  - Hyke, Percy (Box 15)
  - Hyson, Eugene H. (Box 15)
  - I (Box 15)
  - Impara, Virginia (Box 15)
  - Ingram, Ruth (Box 15)
  - Irons, Barbara J. (Box 15)
  - Izambard (Miss) (Box 15)
  - J (Box 15)
  - Jackson, Alice M. (Box 15)
  - Jackson, Ann M. (Box 15)
  - Jackson, Eliza (Box 15)
  - Jackson, Mary (Box 15)
  - Jacobs, Henry R. (Box 15)
  - Jacoby, Doris (Box 15)
  - Jacocks, William P. (Box 15)
  - Jahnes, William G. (Box 16)
  - James, Jane (Box 16)
  - Janover, Evelyn (Box 16)
  - Jeffe, Barbara (Box 16)
  - Johnidis, Ann (Box 16)
  - Johns, Ethel (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Alice Mary (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Everett B. (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Glen L. (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Harald N. (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Henry A. (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Lars (Box 16)
  - Johnson, Loyce (Box 16)
  - Jones, Anne L. (Box 16)
  - Jones, Frank S. (Box 16)
  - Jones, Lauder W. (Box 16)
  - Jones, Phyllis (Box 16)
  - De Jorge, Salime H. (Box 16)
  - Joyner, Gladys S. (Box 16)
  - K (Box 16)
  - Kahin, George M. (Box 16)
  - Kalish, Eleanor (Box 16)
  - Kausch, Dorothy R. (Box 16)
  - Kearney, Harold L. (Box 16)
  - Kelly, Elizabeth R. (Box 16)
  - Kelly, Joan L. (Box 16)
  - Kelly, Kathleen (Box 16)
  - Kelly, Margaret (Box 16)
  - Kelso, Jean (Box 16)
  - Kemps, Virginia (Box 16)
  - Kendricks, John F. (Box 16)
  - Kennahan, Marian (Box 16)
  - Kennedy, Wibert K. (Box 16)
  - Kent, Georgina (Box 16)
  - Kenzell, Madeline (Box 16)
  - Kern, Daniel W. (Box 16)
  - Kerr, Genevieve (Box 16)
  - Kesel, Jane (Box 16)
  - Kester, Roy C. (Box 16)
  - Kibler, W. H. (Box 16)
  - Kieninger, Clara L. (Box 16)
  - Kiernan, Frank E. (Box 16)
  - King, Charles G. (Box 16)
  - King, Dorothy W. (Box 16)
  - King, Ellen Eva (Box 16)
  - King, Katharine B. (Box 16)
  - King, Willard V. (Box 16)
  - King, Woodie Jr. (Box 16)
  - Kirk, Alvira (Box 16)
  - Kitchen, Stuart F. (Box 17)
  - Kittredge, Tracy B. (Box 17)
  - Kleizo, Edward (Box 17)
  - Kligler, L. J. (Box 17)
  - Klotz, Oscar (Box 17)
  - Knapp, Elise (Box 17)
  - Knapp, Gladys (Box 17)
  - Knauth, Alfred (Box 17)
  - Knights, Edwin M. (Box 17)
  - Knowlton, William W. (Box 17)
  - Koch, Lillian E. (Box 17)
  - Kolbe, Harold (Box 17)
  - Kollinay, Francis (Box 17)
  - Kollinay, Joan (Box 17)
  - Kolodin, Irving (Box 17)
  - Kreider, Naome J. (Box 17)
  - Krivickas, Regina (Box 17)
  - Kruger, Constance (Box 17)
  - Kuchinskas, Jean (Box 17)
  - Kulman, Augustus F. (Box 17)
  - L (Box 17)
  - Lacey, Katherine M. (Box 17)
  - Lacy, George R. (Box 17)
  - La Force, Richard J. (Box 17)
  - La Greca, Alice L. (Box 17)
  - Laird, Raymond Lee (Box 17)
  - Lambert, R. A. (Box 17)
  - Lambert, Sylvester M. (Box 17)
  - Landis, Alice Mary (Box 17)
  - Lane, Frederic C. (Box 17)
  - Lanza, Anthony J. (Box 17)
  - LaRoche, Ronald (Box 17)
  - Lathime, Thelma (Box 17)
  - Lathop, Winifred J. (Box 18)
  - Lanbach, Charles A. (Box 18)
  - Lauffer, Max A. (Box 18)
  - Law, Rosa L. (Box 18)
  - Lawrence, Ronald M. (Box 18)
  - Lawson, Marian D. (Box 18)
  - Layton, Dorothy (Box 18)
  - Leach, Charles N. (Box 18)
  - Leach, Sonya J. (Box 18)
  - Leavell, Hugh R. (Box 18)
  - Leemen, Clara M. (Box 18)
  - Lefebre, Germaine (Box 18)
  - Legge, Martine F. (Box 18)
  - Legler, Janet S. (Box 18)
  - Lehman, Lois (Box 18)